<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Devlog</title>
    <link>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Devlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 18:48:00 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fluorescentoast.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automating TikTok Video to YouTube Shorts Without Watermark</title>
      <link>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/automate-tiktok-to-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 18:48:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/automate-tiktok-to-youtube/</guid>
      <description>in recent years, TikTok has become one of the most popular social media platforms. Many people are creating engaging short-form videos on TikTok, and some are even making money from it. Meanwhile, YouTube Shorts has emerged as a new contender in the short-form video space. However, uploading TikTok videos to YouTube Shorts requires a manual and time-consuming process. In this blog post, we will discuss how we can automate this process and upload TikTok videos to YouTube Shorts without the watermark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Session Times With Pine Script</title>
      <link>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/new-york-session-times-with-pine-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 13:22:59 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/new-york-session-times-with-pine-script/</guid>
      <description>In the world of financial trading, it is important to have a clear understanding of the market session times. This information is critical for traders who trade based on market events, news releases, and other market-moving events. In this blog post, we will be discussing a minimalistic approach to visually represent the New York session times on a TradingView chart using Pine Script.
The script uses the New York Session Times as outlined in ICT&amp;rsquo;s 2022 Mentorship videos</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Answering Stackoverflow - Changing the Aspect Ratio of a Video, With Python</title>
      <link>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/stack-overflow-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 13:53:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/stack-overflow-question/</guid>
      <description>And more importantly, answering my first (and probably last) stack overflow question. I had a bunch of videos (300+) and I needed to change the ratio to 9:16, so I could upload them as youtube shorts. No problem I thought, trusty google will solve my problem. Boom. First result is the exact question I&amp;rsquo;m asking for.
Damn. No answers. We&amp;rsquo;re going to have to tackle this on our own.
We are going to be using python&amp;rsquo;s library Moviepy to solve our problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Marketplace Auction Sniper with Python</title>
      <link>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/create-a-marketplace-auction-sniper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 08:50:47 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/create-a-marketplace-auction-sniper/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of missing out on the latest and greatest deals on online marketplaces? Fear not, for with a few lines of Python code, you can create a marketplace auction sniper that will keep you ahead of the curve!
Overview This script is for tracking and sending notifications for new Apple laptop listings on a trading website.
The script does the following steps repeatedly until interrupted:
For each search string in the search_configuration dictionary, it performs a search request with given parameters: search_string, max_buy, number of rows, the canonical path, and page number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang Design Principles for the Chaotic Mind</title>
      <link>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/golang-design-principles-for-the-chaotic-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 09:47:48 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fluorescentoast.github.io/golang-design-principles-for-the-chaotic-mind/</guid>
      <description>Go, or Golang, is one of my favourite languages. Whilst using it at my first job I quickly fell in love. Go&amp;rsquo;s simplicity, readability, and usability make it an ideal choice for programmers with a chaotic mind, as it allowed me to focus on the problem I was trying to solve without getting bogged down in the details.
Simplicity is one of the core design principles stated by Rob Pike.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
